AUNI MOIN

(web developer & sales engineer)

732.829.1575 New York <u>auni.moin@gmail.com</u> <u>linkedin.com/in/aunimoin</u> <u>github.com/aunimoin</u> <u>auni.website</u>

SUMMARY

Highly organized, proactive team player with experience in Web Dev, Digital Ad-Tech and Market Research. Analytic problem-solver with extensive client management expertise who can prioritize tasks and deliver projects under tight deadlines. Specialist in leveraging global team structures and lover of efficient code and elegant web design.

SKILLS

JavaScript, jQuery, JSON, HTML, CSS, React, Node.js, Express, Ruby on Rails, SQL (PostgreSQL & MySQL), Git, MS Word-Excel-Powerpoint, MediaMath's TerminalOne and Nielsen's Spectra, Hispan-IQ & Nitro.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full-Stack Web Dev Immersive at General Assembly, New York

Feb-May, 2018

- Designed and built user friendly, visually appealing apps: Food Trucks Only, Weather, To-Do-List and Pokemon with React and Express on Node; Photo Puzzle with vanilla JavaScript, and Cheeses with RoR.
- Successfully connected with third party APIs Yelp Fusion for food trucks' information and Google Maps for the location of the trucks; OpenWeatherMap for weather data and PokéAPI for Pokemon profiles.
- Developed fluency in full-stack web dev by focusing on best practices of object-oriented programming,
 MVC frameworks, data modeling and pair-programming. Diagnosed bugs via Terminal and Chrome DevTools.

Client Success Consultant at Proleadsoft, New York

2016 - Present

- Outsourcing new clients for an emerging web/mobile development shop based in San Francisco, CA.
- Consulting on best practices pitch, copy, content, and design for Proleadsoft's sales and marketing team.

2016 - 2017

Business Development Manager at Quantformatix, Dhaka, Bangladesh

2015 - 2016

Platform Specialist at MediaMath, New York

- 2013 2014
- Swiftly investigated and resolved Terminal One's (T1) campaign issues; created process documentation; performed data monitoring and troubleshooting with account, sales, product, API and UX/UI teams.
- Prioritized and provided support for almost 2,000 T1 users. Worked with 8 global locations, closed over
 1,700 tickets in 15 months, helped train 7 new support specialists, and maintained client communications.

Associate Client Manager at The Nielsen Company, New York

2010 - 2012

- Created detailed reports (120/year) for Mars Chocolate and Wrigley Gum's marketing and sales teams by translating raw data to provide insights on consumer targeting, segmentation and consumption analyses.
- Trained more than 50 analysts, managers, and directors on Nielsen's Spectra software.

Biz Dev Mrg & Market Analyst for Crowd Interactive, Boxhouse.org and BAMS.com, Brooklyn

2008 - 2010

Process Engineer, Project Manager & Internal Consultant at Gerdau Ameristeel, Perth Amboy, NJ

2004 - 2007

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Electrical Engineering - Missouri University of Science and Technology

2004

Web Dev Immersive Program - Certificate of Completion - General Assembly

Feb-May, 2018

LANGUAGES & INTERESTS

Fluent in Bengali. Bicycling, yoga, soccer, tennis, creating exotic chutneys/dips, sketching/painting, and rescuing/fostering cats and dogs for BrooklynAnimalAction.org.